wgtools.com 2011-12-04

# WGTools.com • Privacy Policy

At wgtools.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by wgtools.com and how it is used. We also will **_never_** sell your personal information to third parties.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, wgtools.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
WGTools.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Examples of our advertising partners are BurstMedia, Google Adsense and CPX Interactive.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements that appear on wgtools.com sent directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Also, the same concept is used with advertisements such as Google Adsense (Interest-based advertising) to collect information about the user's surfing habits, for example if a user visits many sporting websites Google Adsense will try to show relevant advertisement, in this example for sporting.

Interest-based advertising enables advertisers to reach users based on their interests (e.g. "sports enthusiasts"), and allows them to show ads based on a user's previous interactions with them, such as visits to advertiser websites. To complement interest-based advertising, the [Google Ads Preferences Manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/) lets users view and edit their interest categories.

Google's use of the [DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
